mdgadvertising.com 2018-02-17

# MDG Advertising - Marketing And Advertising Agency Boca Raton | Michael Del Gigante, Eric Norstrom, Joanne Pennisi, Karen Bleier, Hillary Lis, Julia Giordano, Schuyler Meder

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. 

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience

(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide, may be used to send you information and updates, in addition to receiving occasional company news, related products or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

## Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.mdgadvertising.com  
3500 nw boca raton blvd  
boca raton, Florida 33431  
United States
